[{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Pure water effectively conducts electricity ", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Kraft &quot;Cheez Whiz&quot; contains cheese culture, but doesn&#039;t actually contain cheese", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The commercial UK channel ITV stands for &quot;International Television&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Did Michael Jackson invent the moonwalk?", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "French is an official language in Canada.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "In Scandinavian languages, the letter &Aring; means river.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Stagecoach owned &quot;South West Trains&quot; before losing the rights to FirstGroup and MTR in March of 2017.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanksgiving", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "In architecture, a &quot;pecklesteiner&quot; is a set of doors that overlap each other when closed, and can be locked through a single keyhole.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "King Gizzard &amp; The Lizard Wizard&#039;s album &quot;Nonagon Infinity&quot; can be looped seamlessly.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "&quot;Typewriter&quot; is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "In Scandinavian languages, the letter &Aring; means river.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "In architecture, a &quot;pecklesteiner&quot; is a set of doors that overlap each other when closed, and can be locked through a single keyhole.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Spoon theory is a theory, utilizing &quot;Spoons&quot; as a metaphor for energy they can use in a day.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide is a dangerous chemical.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "&quot;Typewriter&quot; is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "This is the correct spelling of &quot;Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Did Michael Jackson invent the moonwalk?", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Pure water effectively conducts electricity ", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "SCP-173 was the first SCP article written for the web-based collaborative fiction project known as the &quot;SCP Foundation&quot;", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Spoon theory is a theory, utilizing &quot;Spoons&quot; as a metaphor for energy they can use in a day.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "SCP-173 was the first SCP article written for the web-based collaborative fiction project known as the &quot;SCP Foundation&quot;", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The commercial UK channel ITV stands for &quot;International Television&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The word &quot;news&quot; originates from the first letters of the 4 main directions on a compass (North, East, West, South).", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Stagecoach owned &quot;South West Trains&quot; before losing the rights to FirstGroup and MTR in March of 2017.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Kraft &quot;Cheez Whiz&quot; contains cheese culture, but doesn&#039;t actually contain cheese", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "The average woman is 5 inches / 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s life expectancy.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Spoon theory is a theory, utilizing &quot;Spoons&quot; as a metaphor for energy they can use in a day.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]